https://janestaffordtextiles.com/privacy/

Currency conversions are estimated and should be used for informational purposes only.
CADUSDEURGBPAUD
Spend over $250 and you'll receive free shipping! Receive 10% off & free shipping when you spend over $500. (Some Exceptions Apply)
Home / Privacy Policy
Who we are
The responsible data controller for this website is Jane Stafford.
Jane Stafford 142 Richard Flack Road Salt Spring Island, BC. V8K 2P5, Canada Email: privacy@janestaffordtextiles.com
You can contact us any time via email or the postal address above, if you have questions about our privacy policy.
How we collect your data
This is an overview of how we handle your personal data. Please see the sections below for further details.
On this website
https://janestaffordtextiles.com
Unless you choose to shop with us, we don’t collect any personal data on our website except server logs.
Store
https://janestaffordtextiles.com/shop/
Our store is hosted on our website. If you choose to shop with us then we will have to collect some personal information, but only as much as is necessary to complete the purchase.
Forum
https://janestaffordtextiles.com/forums/forum/weaving-discussion/
Our support forum is hosted on our website. Any personally identifying information you might enter whilst posting on the forum is stored on our website.
Newsletter
https://janestaffordtextiles.com/newsletter-sign-up/
If you sign up to our newsletter, your data is being collected by our newsletter service, MailChimp.
Your rights
You can exercise your rights by sending us an email at privacy@janestaffordtextiles.com.
You can access information on all data stored about you
Get in contact and we will provide you with all information on data we have about you.
You have the right to be ‘forgotten’ by us
Let us know and we will delete all your personal data that we store.
You have the right to correct any personal data stored about you
If there’s any personal data about you that should be corrected by us, please let us know.
You have the right to withdraw your consent
If you signed up to our forum or subscribed to our newsletter you can always delete your forum account or unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time. You can do this on your own on the forum or with the unsubscribe button in our newsletters. But we are also happy to do this for you, if you want. Just let us know.
You have the right to port your data to another service
We will give you a copy of your data in a plain text format so that you can provide it to another service.
You have the right to file a complaint regarding our use of your data
Please tell us first, so we have a chance to address your concerns. If we fail in this, you can address any complaint to your national data protection authorities.
Website
Cookies
Our website uses WooCommerce cookies, Wordfence cookies and Google Analytics cookies. We only use cookies to enhance the functionality on the website and do not use cookies to attempt to identify you for the purposes of processing your data in any way.
Analytics and tracking
Our website uses Google Analytics to provide us with anonymised analytics data. Google Analytics anonymizes IP addresses. We do not use Google Analytics User ID. We do not use Google Analytics Display and Search Remarketing. We do not link our Google Analytics data to Google Adwords, Google AdSense or Google Ad Exchange. Our Google Analytics user and event data retention period is 26 months.
TLS encryption
This site uses TLS encryption for security reasons and to protect the transmission of confidential data. You can recognize an encrypted connection in your browser’s address line when it changes from “http://” to “https://” and when the lock icon is displayed in your browser’s address bar.
If TLS encryption is activated, the data you transfer to us cannot be read by third parties.
Hosting
The server for our website is provided by
SG Hosting Inc.
901 N. Pitt St, Suite 325,
Alexandria 22314 VA
The server is located in their data centre in Chicago, USA. You can find their terms and policies here: https://www.siteground.com/terms.htm
Server log files
We automatically collect and store information that your browser transmits to us in “server log files” on our server. These are:
Browser type and browser version
Operating system used
Referrer URL
Host name of the accessing computer
Time of the server request
IP address
This data will not be combined with data from other sources.
Third-party services
We use the following third-party services on our website:
Canada Post
We use Canada Post to obtain shipping rates. The address you enter is transmitted to Canada Post before a purchase is made.
Canada Post Privacy Office,
2701 Riverside Dr., N1140, OTTAWA ON K1A 0B1, Canada
You can find their privacy policy here: https://www.canadapost.ca/web/en/kb/details.page?article=privacystatementfo&cattype=kb&cat=generalinquiries
Store
After purchasing we store the information you supplied on our website, with the exception of your credit card details.
Third-party services
We use the following third-parties to service our customers:
Moneris
We use Moneris as a payment provider.
Moneris Solutions Privacy Officer
P.O. Box 219, Station D Toronto, ON M6P 3J8
Information shared with a payment provider to process payments includes:
Name
Email
Address
Phone
City/State/Zip
Unique payment identifier
Payment provider identifier
You can find their privacy policy here: https://www.moneris.com/en/Privacy-Policy
PayPal
We use PayPal as a payment provider.
PayPal
2211 North First Street
San Jose, CA 95131, USA
You can find their privacy policy here: https://www.paypal.com/ca/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full?locale.x=en_CA
ShipStation
We use ShipStation as our shipping provider. Information shared with a shipping provider includes city and zip code, to calculate shipping rates.
Auctane d/b/a ShipStation
3800 N Lamar Blvd #220
Austin, TX 78756, USA
You can find their privacy policy here: https://www.shipstation.com/privacy-policy/
Xero
If you make a purchase from us, we store your details in our accounting application. We use Xero as our accounting application provider.
XERO ONE
19-23 Taranaki St
Te Aro
Wellington 6011, New Zealand
You can find their privacy policy here: https://www.xero.com/ca/about/privacy/
DEAR Systems
If you make a purchase on our website, we store your details in our inventory system. We use DEAR Systems to maintain our inventory data.
Office 707, Jumeirah Lake Towers,
Cluster C, Fortune Tower, Dubai, UAE
You can find their privacy policy here: https://dearsystems.com/inventory-software/privacy-policy/
Square
We use Square for in-store purchases and invoicing.
Square, Inc.
1455 Market Street, Suite 600
San Francisco, CA 94103, USA
You can find their privacy policy here: https://squareup.com/legal/privacy
Help Scout
If you email us or we contact you by email then it’s likely that your email will be stored in our help desk management application. We use Help Scout to manage our help desk.
Attn: Privacy Agent
Help Scout Inc.
131 Tremont Street
3rd Floor
Boston, MA 02111-1338, USA
You can find their privacy policy here: https://www.helpscout.net/company/legal/privacy/
Support Forum
Our support forum is hosted on our website.
Newsletter
You can sign up to our monthly newsletter to receive news and updates. To sign up we require your email address and you can provide an optional name.
All subscriber data is collected by our newsletter service MailChimp:
The Rocket Science Group, LLC
675 Ponce de Leon Ave NE
Suite 5000
Atlanta, GA 30308 USA
You can find their privacy policy here: https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/
MailChimp attempts to check if newsletters have been opened and links have been clicked. We only use those analytics to check how interesting and relevant our newsletters are for the entire list of subscribers over time. We never use them to analyze individual subscribers.
You can unsubscribe from our newsletter at any time. This can be done by using the unsubscribe link in every newsletter or by sending an email to privacy@janestaffordtextiles.com and we will handle it for you.
Questions & Feedback
We try to keep our privacy policy as transparent and easy to understand as possible. Please let us know if we can improve it further or if you have any other questions: privacy@janestaffordtextiles.com
Updates
We will check and update this privacy policy if necessary.
Last update: Dec 11, 2019
Weave a Path to Excellenceup to 3 hours of new video every 5 weeks!For weavers of all levelsComplete access to every past videoLearn more
Recent posts
The Lace Weaves are coming in 2021!
JST Blog October Weaver Spotlight!
August 2020 Newsletter
JST Blog August Weaver Spotlight!
July Newsletter
Recent commentsGinette on Online Guild Index (beta version)Jeannette Frantz on Online Guild Index (beta version)Ginette on Online Guild Index (beta version)Francine on Online Guild Index (beta version)Kristina on In Praise of Good Selvedges: Practical Tips for Weavers
Unparalleled service and next day shipping
We offer unparalleled service, with next-day shipping on most items, and over 40 years of weaving and teaching experience to draw on, for knowledgeable, inspirational support.
Create a new list
&cross
Subscribe to our newsletter for the latest news and inspiration from Jane Stafford Textiles each month!
